SPECIAL THANKS TO NATIONAL FILM DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION MALAYSIA
LICENSING PRODUCTION SPP 11936
NAMES , EVENTS , AND STORIES ADOPTED OR MENTIONED IN THIS FILM ARE FICTIONAL
RESEMBLANCE TO REAL EVENTS IS COINCIDENTAL
Zulaikha .
Honey ...
There is no deity except God .
There is no deity ...
except God .
And Muhammad is the Messenger of God .
And Muhammad ...
is the Messenger ...
of God .
Oh God , why ?
Why ?
Oh , God !
THREE MONTHS LATER
KORAN
Hurry up , Maria .
What took you so long in the kitchen ?
Is it so hard to make a drink ?
If so , I 'll make it myself next time .
It 's not a big deal .
Relax , Zeti .
Maria is your stepdaughter .
Don 't make her feel bad .
It 's not because she 's my stepdaughter .
I love her despite being almost the same age as her .
I treat her like my own daughter .
Do you really love my daughter ?
Maria .
Did you open this ?
Amir , come here .
Amir , you 've grown up .
Stop playing with toys like a little kid .
Dad ,
I dreamed about Mom .
And she told me that she 's coming back soon .
Do you miss your mom ?
As much as I do ?
Yes .
Dad , when will Mom be coming back ?
Amir , she has passed away .
Every living thing in this world has a lifetime .
There will come a day
when that lifetime will end , just like your mom 's .
I understand .
- But Mom - - - Amir .
She has passed away .
She won 't be coming back anymore .
Dad , can you accept the truth that she has passed away ?
You don 't love her , do you ?
Amir , it 's not that I don 't love her - - Amir !
Amen .
When you 've grown up ,
I might not be here anymore .
Remember to visit our graves
because it will remind you of death and the Afterlife .
Remember what I said .
Why do you want to meet me today ?
If we are here for personal matters , then no thanks .
As your boss ,
I have the right to know about your personal matters .
I also have the right to know what is happening to you .
What do you mean ?
Where did you get these pills ?
- Did you go through my things ? - You were not like this , Maria .
Why did you suddenly become depressed ?
Tell me what 's wrong .
Just tell me your problem . Perhaps I can help you .
It 's none of your business !
Maria .
You know that I care about you .
Can we be like how we used to be ?
I miss the old you .
Bring her back .
I 'm leaving .
Excuse me .
Ustaz .
- Peace be upon you , Shah . - And peace be upon you too .
- How are you , Ustaz ? - I 'm good .
Shah , how 's your wife doing ?
Is she getting better ?
Thanks to your treatment , she 's doing fine now .
No more screaming like before .
She is getting better not because of me , Shah .
I did my best to heal her ,
but God made it happen .
I heard that you 've stopped helping the people in the village , is that true ?
Dad , what happened ?
Here , have a drink , Azman .
How much longer do you want to be like this , Adam ?
Can you stop isolating yourself at home ?
Imam Ali and the others from the mosque are all concerned about you .
When do you want to start working ?
Are you going to leave your farm and your garden like that ?
Remember , Adam . Our jobs are a form of worship to God .
Any updates regarding the hit-and-run accident ?
Haven 't the police found out who caused my wife 's death ?
Just leave it to God , Adam .
I know that I 'm not in your position .
And I understand what you 're going through right now .
I just want to remind you of one thing .
Please come back to our mosque because - -
There is no better place to seek peace other than the mosque .
I understand , Azman .
I really do , but ...
Hey , Adam .
Have faith !
Since I 've known you , I know you are not ...
a grumpy and vengeful person .
What 's wrong with you , Adam ?
I 'm your best friend and I care about you , Adam .
You know it , don 't you ?
We can be impulsive and reckless .
Our faith falters at times .
We have to be careful !
Throw your vengeance spite away .
Learn how to forgive !
I won 't forgive them .
That will never happen .
I won 't forgive the person who caused her death .
It 's Zulaikha , my wife , you know ?
Don 't blame me for acting this way .
Blame the person who took my happiness away .
This person murdered my wife !
Adam .
REPENTANCE
SPIRIT amp ; SATAN IN HUMAN 'S LIFE
THE PSYCHOLOGY OF SATAN
SATANIC MOVEMENT
Indeed , Satan is an enemy to you .
So take him for an enemy .
Satan is the one who wants to make you his inmates in the burning Hell .
Did I not enjoin upon you , O children of Adam ?
Do not worship Satan
because Satan is your absolute enemy .
God , have mercy !
Please turn the lights on !
God , have mercy on us .
What 's wrong ? What happened ? I saw you rushing out of the lift .
Did someone bother you ?
In life ,
we have to face two things .
Firstly , the catastrophe .
Secondly , blessings .
As a human being , we have to accept the truth .
That 's easy for you to say , Imam .
Maybe because you 've never been in my shoes .
I know that salvation doesn 't come easy ,
but sometimes I think ,
" Why did God give me such a difficult test ? "
All of the answers about life are stated in the Koran
and God has answered all of your questions .
God won 't burden us beyond what we can endure .
Ask God for guidance
to lift you off from the burden so that your heart will be at peace .
It 's good if you can forgive the person who caused your wife 's death .
No , Imam . It 's not that easy .
It 's impossible for me to forgive that person .
Adam .
God knows everything .
As long as you don 't forgive them ,
you won 't be at peace .
You won 't find out who killed your wife if you behave like this .
If God is willing ,
once you have forgiven the person who did this ,
God will guide you .
God will open your heart
and your eyes to the truth .
God , have mercy on us .
I don 't know what 's wrong with your daughter .
Supposedly , people of faith ,
if they pray often , their souls should be at peace ,
but she seems more depressed every day .
Even though she 's like that , I 'm so thankful
because faith doesn 't come without hardship .
Honey , what is her problem exactly ?
She seems to be hiding something from us . Did she become depressed because of me ?
I feel uneasy around her .
I 'm like a stranger to her .
Maybe she has other things bothering her .
I 'll talk to her myself .
What bothers me is that
she 's been studying about Satan in the Koran and the Hadith .
She could study other things .
The Koran is not only about Satan and evil spirits .
Damn it .
Such a bother .
Thank you so much , Fazli .
You helped Maria
fix her car
and sent her home last night .
I was just passing by .
If I wasn 't there , I don 't know what would 've happened to Maria .
Didn 't I tell you that I care about you ?
I know your situation .
What do you mean ?
What 's wrong with me ?
I 'm sorry if I 've been troubling you guys .
It 's okay , Zeti .
By the way , have you told her about my plan on marrying her ?
I can take care of her .
I understand , but it 's not the right time to tell her yet .
If not now , how long do I still need to wait ?
Zulaikha .
Zulaikha !
Please accept the truth
no matter how sad you are .
God will turn your life around
and bless you with the life you may not have expected .
God ...
God .
God knows everything , honey .
I ...
I miss you , Zulaikha .
Many people desire salvation .
And many people long with their whole heart to embrace God
because of the suffering of the world .
Wait for me , Zulaikha .
God , have mercy on us .
Amir misses you too .
Dad .
Dad !
- What 's wrong , Amir ? - Grandpa is here .
Come .
Dad , why didn 't you call me before you came ?
Because I knew you would be at home .
Anyway , I won 't be here long , just a couple of days .
How are you ?
I 've been great .
Amir is on a school break .
At least , he can keep me company .
Actually ,
your mom is the one who asked me to come and visit you .
She 's been worrying about you .
She told me
that she had bad dreams about you .
What did she even dream about ?
- I 'm sure I 'm going to be okay . - Really ?
Are you sure you are fine ?
- Perhaps - - - Dad .
Let me show you to your room .
God , have mercy on us .
Maria ?
Maria ...
Peace be upon you , Imam .
Yes .
Then what now , Imam ?
If you are free , please come and help Mr. Osman 's daughter .
She is from the same village as us .
According to Mr. Osman 's wife , she 's very ill .
I ...
It 's not that I don 't want to help , Imam .
How about this , Imam ?
You can call Ustaz Saiful .
I think he can help you out .
I 'm not free right now .
Ustaz Saiful isn 't available at the moment , Adam .
He will only be coming back from Mecca next week .
Please help , Adam .
Perhaps now is the time for you to come back to work .
To help and perform the ruqyah on the villagers .
All right , Imam .
I 'll be right over .
Go ahead , Adam .
It 's been a while since you stopped curing people .
Please don 't waste the abilities
that God has given you .
Peace be upon you .
And peace be upon you too .
Could you explain to us what happened ?
Ustaz Adam needs to know that .
I was in the kitchen doing some chores .
Then I heard Maria screaming .
When I found her , she was already lying on the floor .
- How is she now ? - I was trying to calm her down ,
but she pushed me away and stormed off to the living room .
What 's your opinion , Adam ?
I 'm sorry for asking .
Are there any talismans in your house ?
Talismans to protect your house ?
We have to hurry , Adam .
- Can we go and have a look ? - Sure .
Her room is at the far end of the house .
Maria , we are here to help you .
But you have to calm down
and say your prayers .
If you can 't recite it in your mouth ,
- then recite it in your heart . - Azman .
Help me , Ustaz .
Please help me , Ustaz .
This Imam has taken a liking to me .
He did this to me , Ustaz .
Get rid of him .
I have never missed a single prayer session .
I pray day and night .
I wake up every night to perform night prayers
so I can worship God !
Glory be to God . Praise be to God . There is no God but God . God is Great !
Stop lying , you cursed Satan .
Stop the facade .
- I seek refuge from God . - In the name of God .
In the name of God , the beneficent , the merciful .
Wherever you may be , God will bring you forth for judgment altogether .
Indeed , God is over all things competent .
God , have mercy on us .
Adam , where 's Maria ?
Maria ! Maria !
Where did she go , Adam ?
Maria .
Adam , where did Maria go ?
God , have mercy on us .
I 've worshiped God thousands of years ago !
God created me to be His best creation !
I am a Muslim genie !
I want to help this woman !
A good , God-fearing Muslim genie will not harm and mislead humans .
Since you 're hurting this woman , you are nothing but evil !
Leave this woman 's body .
Otherwise , I 'll destroy you in the name of God .
I will harm you with His permission !
- Leave ! - You deserve to be thrown into Hell !
You deserve to die !
I seek refuge in God from Satan the outcast .
In the name of God , the beneficent , the merciful .
We said , " Fear not . Indeed , it is you who are superior .
And throw what is in your right hand ; it will swallow up what they have crafted .
It is but the trick of a magician
and the magician will not succeed wherever he is . "
So the magicians fell down in prostration .
They said , " We believe in the Lord of Aaron and Moses . "
Keep going , Azman !
You deserve to die !
May you live in blasphemy and turn yourself from Islam !
Non-believers !
- Infidel . - Apostates !
- Hypocrites ! - Renegade .
My sole purpose is to make Muslims go astray !
So the truth was established and abolished was what they were doing .
And Pharaoh and his people were overcome right there and became debased .
And the magicians fell down in prostration to God .
They said , " We have believed in the Lord of the worlds ,
the Lord of Moses and Aaron . "
God is Great !
I seek refuge in God from Satan the outcast .
In the name of God , the beneficent , the merciful .
God is Great !
You filthy humans .
What kind of spell are you using ?
Who are you ?
I am Adam , a servant of God , and an enemy of Satan .
Get lost ! I won 't get out of here !
Leave , you cursed Satan !
Leave this woman 's body .
I won 't leave this woman 's body .
- In the name of God . - If I do so , my master won 't feed me .
- And when they had thrown , Moses said , - In the name of God .
" Indeed , God will expose its worthlessness .
Indeed , God does not amend the work of corrupters .
And God will establish the truth by His words ,
even if the criminals dislike it . "
But no one believed Moses ,
except for some youths among his people , for fear of Pharaoh - -
There 's one more evil force coming .
Watch out !
He 's a descendant of Satan !
He 'll mislead all the followers of the Prophet
and turn them against the Koran !
Who amongst you will come against us , you cursed Satan ?
Dajjal !
Glory be to God . Praise be to God . There is no God but God . God is Great !
He is the All-Hearing the All-Knowing .
Maria .
- There is no power nor strength - My goodness .
except in God , the Lofty , the Great .
There is no power nor strength except in God , the Lofty , the Great .
There are none worthy of worship besides you .
Glorified are you . Surely , I 'm from among the wrongdoers .
How is she , Adam ?
Is everything settled ?
It 's complicated , Imam .
Somebody has sent an evil spirit to disturb her .
Maria vomited nails just now .
I 'm sure she has been cursed .
Has she fully recovered ?
Such evil spirits have many ways of corrupting innocence .
We can pray for her for now .
What is happening to our community ?
Is there no end to this madness ?
- Shame on us . - Shame on us or shame on religion ?
Which one do you think is worse ?
All right , Azman .
Help me perform the call of prayer in each room of the house .
- Imam , feel free to help him . - All right .
I hope Ustaz can come and visit Maria again .
Before this ,
I sought help elsewhere ,
but her condition is still getting worse .
As human beings , we shouldn 't be afraid of Satan .
As long as God honors the likes of man ,
we are better than evil spirits in the eyes of God .
I understand , but when will this end ?
Until when ?
I can 't stand it anymore .
- Should I call other people for help ? - Everything happens because of Him .
Have strong beliefs in the Koran and Sunnah .
The reason why Maria hasn 't recovered yet
isn 't because Islam is weak ,
but it is us who are weak .
Sorry , I was in a meeting when you called me .
How 's Maria ?
I 'm not sure , but she 's inside the house now .
Luckily Ustaz Adam was here to help .
Why did you ask for their help ?
How much do you have to pay ? RM100 or RM200 ?
You must 've had to donate to the mosque before they even lifted a finger .
Adam .
Peace be upon you .
Why were you being so rude to them , Fazli ?
They 've been a part of our village 's mosque for a long time !
People nowadays disguise themselves as religious leaders to cheat our money .
You saw what they were wearing just now .
The outfits are sold everywhere .
I 've been cheated by these kinds of people more than once .
I don 't want you to end up being cheated by them .
Many people will try to cheat you since you 're a woman .
YOU HAVE TO COME BACK TO ME , ZULAIKHA !
AMIR REALLY NEEDS YOU !
Dad , what are you doing in my bedroom ? What are you looking for ?
Nothing , I was just looking around .
Dad .
Is it wrong , Dad ?
Is it wrong for a husband to miss his late wife ?
Of course , it 's not wrong .
- But you - - - Is it wrong for me to express
my feelings to my late wife in this letter ?
You think I 'm a bad person
by hiding something from you ?
I 've never thought of that , Adam .
I 'm just confused .
There are a lot of things I don 't understand .
You must have been having bad thoughts about me .
If not , you wouldn 't have come into my room .
Zulaikha has just ...
She has just passed away , Dad .
You should support me at this moment , instead of ...
Maria , where 's my stuff ?
You better give it back to me now !
What stuff ? I 've never taken your stuff .
Stop lying ! I saw you holding it the other day .
What stuff ?
You mean the small box ?
Who else other than you would take my stuff ?
Where did you hide it ?
- What are you doing ? - Where did you put it ?
- I 've never taken your stuff . - It is very important and priceless to me !
I swear to God , I 've never taken your stuff .
Hey , you 've been distracted the whole day .
How about this , Fazli ?
You don 't know how to treat her right , that 's why she rejected you .
Why would she reject me ?
I 've told her we would be getting married .
Why are you so desperate to marry her ?
Come on , she 's pretending to be religious .
What a hypocrite .
Mind your words .
It 's my choice whether to marry her or not .
It 's none of your business .
I 'm asking you right now , how long you intend to wait ?
I know Maria 's dad is rich despite him being a village man .
I think this is a game .
Do you desire her dad 's assets ?
Maybe her dad is sick because of the thing that you sent him .
- It worked ? - Yes , that 's why we are talking about it .
I didn 't know you 're the type to do that .
Hey , Fazli ! Are you crazy ?
Fazli ! God , have mercy on us .
Fazli , do you want to kill him ?
Hey , you 're killing him ! Fazli !
Stop it !
Have you lost your mind ?
Are you crazy ? Son of a bitch .
Hey . My goodness .
Maria .
Where are you going ?
If you are still mad at me ,
I 'm sorry .
I can 't stand this anymore .
Your dad is sick , so are you .
I 'm all alone .
I 'm lost !
Your heart is black ! You 're rotten to the core !
I know you are happy when I 'm sick .
You want my dad to die so that you can inherit his fortune !
You are the troublemaker of our family !
A wench like you will face the consequences !
Why did you slap me , Maria ?
Maria !
Let go of me , Maria !
It hurts ! Let go of me !
God , have mercy . Let go of me , Maria .
Please let go of me .
Hey .
Amir , what are you doing in my bedroom ?
When did you come in ? Why aren 't you sleeping with Grandpa ?
I dreamed about Mom .
She said she 'll be back tonight ,
but I 'm scared
because Mom is very angry with you this time .
God , have mercy on us . Amir .
Why did you dream about such things ?
Come on .
Let 's go to Grandpa 's room .
Peace be upon you .
And peace be - -
Don 't answer her , Amir .
Dad ?
Is Grandpa in his bedroom , Amir ?
Dad , is that you ?
Dad !
- Amir , wait for me here . - Okay .
Maria , listen .
How many times have I told you ?
I love you and I want to marry you .
I mean it .
Maria , do you hear what I am saying ?
Do you know why I don 't want to get married to you ?
Because I 'm falling in love with the guy who helped me .
Ustaz Adam .
Nowadays , it 's difficult to find this kind of person .
A person of faith
whose heart is filled with doubt .
What is your relationship with him ?
Maria , you have to think about his intentions .
He is just using you .
Don 't trust him , Maria .
He 's a cheater !
Don 't believe a single word he says .
Stop being so obsessed with him .
To make things clear , I want you to tell you this .
I already slept with him .
Honey , Maria tried to kill me just now .
She slapped me and dragged me across the floor .
Who does she think I am ?
I 'm her stepmom , not some stranger .
Is this true ?
We are only married for one year and you want - -
You think I 'm making this up ?
You think I 'm slandering her ?
Her condition is getting worse .
She wasn 't herself when she was talking to me just now .
I 'll call Ustaz Adam to come and help Maria .
I heard a ruckus this morning . What 's wrong ?
I had an argument with Maria .
I thought she took my box , but it wasn 't her .
I think your best friend , Imam Ali , has taken it .
Doesn 't he visit you often ?
The problem is , the thing inside the box is alive .
Goodness !
God , have mercy !
God , have mercy - -
Maria .
It 's okay .
Let her be .
In the name of God , the beneficent , the merciful .
God , send blessings to Muhammad and his family .
O God , send blessings to Muhammad and his family .
There are none worthy of worship besides you .
Glorified are you . Surely , I 'm from among the wrongdoers .
You are my greatest enemy on earth !
True believers like you !
In the name of God , the beneficent , the merciful .
There is no deity except Him .
The Ever-Living , the sustainer of existence .
Neither drowsiness overtakes Him nor sleep .
To Him belongs whatever is in the heavens and whatever is on the earth .
Who is it that can intercede with Him except by His permission ?
- He knows what is presently before them ... - I will make you fear everything
- And they encompass not a thing ... - except God !
Except for what He wills .
His Kursi extends over the heavens and the earth .
And their preservation tires Him not . And He is the Most High , the Most Great !
God , have mercy ! Hold her !
I seek refuge in God from Satan the outcast .
In the name of God , the beneficent , the merciful .
And We inspired to Moses , " Throw your staff , " and at once ,
- it devoured what they were falsifying . - I want human beings to weep !
... and abolished was what they were doing .
- Pharaoh and his people were overcome ... - And burn with me in Hell !
And the magicians fell down in prostration to God .
They said , " We have believed in the Lord of the worlds ,
the Lord of Moses and Aaron . "
We seek refuge in Your names , dear God .
Leave now !
Hurry up , Zeti .
Zeti , get back !
The Ever-Living , the sustainer of existence .
Neither drowsiness overtakes Him nor sleep .
To Him belongs whatever is in the heavens and whatever is on the earth .
Who is it that can intercede with Him except by His permission ?
He knows what is presently ...
Watch her , Zeti !
Maria .
- In the name of God . - My goodness .
- Sir , I 'm sorry , but you can 't enter . - I want to see Imam !
- Sorry , sir . - Sir !
Can I see him ?
In the name of God , the beneficent , the merciful .
God , have mercy on us .
Goodness .
Mr. Osman !
Ustaz !
Why were you screaming ?
What happened ?
- Mr . Osman is missing . - What ?
What ? Wasn 't he in his bedroom just now ?
Yes , but he 's missing now !
Your husband is not here ! Do you understand ?
What ? Oh , God .
What should we do ?
Ustaz , where are you going ?
- Peace be upon you , Azman . - And peace be upon you too .
Adam , Imam Ali ...
Imam Ali passed away about an hour ago .
What ?
Indeed we belong to God , and indeed to Him we will return .
- Where are you now ? - His body was found at Batu 16 .
Adam , come here quickly .
Goodness , how can this be happening ?
- Was he in a car crash ? - I don 't know .
The police are still investigating it .
But from what I 've heard , something strange happened to him .
What is happening ? Adam , please come here quickly .
Something strange ? What are you talking about ?
I 'm wondering if Imam Ali 's death has something to do with Maria .
Even Mr. Osman , Maria 's dad , is missing now !
Yes , Amir ?
Why are you suddenly calling me ?
I 'll come home later .
Can you pass my call to Grandpa ?
He is not at home .
He 's been out for a long time .
I don 't know where he went .
Where did he go ?
How could he leave you alone at home ?
It 's all right . Mom is here with me .
Please stop saying that , Amir .
I 've had enough of that nonsense .
Don 't worry , Dad . Mom is taking care of me right now .
Don 't you understand ?
I 've told you many times not to mention her !
I don 't want to hear about it , do you understand me ?
You 're driving me crazy by asking about her every day , you know ?
Why don 't you understand ? Are you deaf ?
Please forgive me , Zulaikha .
Please forgive me .
Amir !
Stop right there !
- Where do you think you 're going ? - Dad !
- Wake up ! - Dad !
- Dad , stop ! - You want to see your mom so much , right ?
- Dad , stop ! - You miss your mom so much , right ?
- You want to see her , right ? - Dad , let go of me !
- Here she is ! See for yourself ! - Dad !
She 's right in front of you now , Amir .
I ...
I went to her grave and dug her body out for you !
Just for you , Amir .
I did this because I love you .
This is what I have to do .
I assure you .
After this , you will forget about your mom .
And I don 't want you to say that you miss her anymore !
You will forget about her forever .
What are you waiting for ? Go hug and kiss her !
Express all of your feelings towards her !
Dad , you are crazy !
Hey , stop right there !
You 've been giving me shit all this while !
Where are you going ? I 'm losing my mind because of you !
Screw you , bastard !
How dare you !
Dad , please ...
You should die !
I seek refuge in God from Satan the outcast .
What else do we need to investigate about Imam 's death ?
There 's nothing else to be investigated .
Let us accept the truth that he has passed away .
Goodness .
I have a bad feeling .
Do you remember what I told you last night ?
I have a strong hunch that Imam Ali 's death is related to Maria .
What 's the meaning behind all of this ?
Can you please stop talking about Maria ?
Tell me .
What does Maria have to do with his death ?
I don 't think so , Adam .
What we should do now is pray for Imam so that he can rest in peace !
- The problem is - - - What else ?
You are the one with the problem . You are doubtful !
What are you looking for ?
You 're my best friend .
But sometimes , I don 't know what is on your mind
ever since your wife - -
Peace be upon you .
- And peace be upon you too . - We are the police .
We would like to see Mr. Adam regarding the missing of Maria 's dad .
I see .
Adam .
The police are here to seek your help regarding Maria 's dad .
I don 't understand .
In the Koran ,
why does God refers to Himself
as " I " and at other times " We " ?
Can you
stop disturbing me ?
Don 't you feel sad for what has happened ?
But I want to know why !
Why does God refer to Himself as " We " !
Goodness , Maria .
What kind of question is that ?
Don 't you know the answer ?
What have you been studying ?
Because someone came to me in my dream and told me
- that God refers to Himself and - - - God , have mercy on us .
Maria , it was Satan who was talking to you in your dream .
And you believed what it said to you ?
When God uses " We " ,
it means He refers to His greatness !
Do you understand ?
Pray to God , Maria !
Peace be upon you .
Why are you outside ?
Didn 't my dad invite you in ?
What 's the matter - -
Hypocrites like you
can fool anyone , but me .
People like you have no respect !
God , have mercy .
What 's wrong with you ?
Why are you suddenly slandering me ?
Stop acting like an angel !
Stop being a hypocrite !
How many other women have you slept with ?
Who knows if you slept with married women .
Maria told me everything .
You do know she is not well , right ?
You shouldn 't believe what she says .
Her words might not be her own , but Satan 's !
Hypocrites like you don 't get to talk to me about religion !
You don 't fool me , you false prophet !
Instead of God , people like you worship their own desires !
Keep in mind .
Sooner or later , everyone will know the real you .
Adam !
Go away !
Get away from me !
If you mess with me , I 'll kill you !
You are the reason my dad is missing , aren 't you ?
Stay away from me !
Move closer and I 'll kill you .
God , have mercy on us .
Maria , what 's wrong with you ?
What did you think I was going to do ?
I just wanted to give you this cup of prayer water .
Instead of God , people like you worship their own desires !
Keep in mind .
Sooner or later , everyone will know the real you .
Adam .
Before the situation gets worse , I would like to talk to you for a while .
- Actually - - - What do you want to say , Dad ?
I saw you chatting with Shah at the graveyard just now .
Did he bad-mouth me ?
Adam , please don 't judge him wrongly .
He has no malicious intent .
He told me that he saw - -
What ?
Dad , he broke into this house once .
Is that what you call a good person ?
And you are asking me not to judge him wrongly ?
Adam , please let me talk first !
If you still want to tell me how good Shah is , forget it .
I don 't trust that man at all .
Perhaps he has something to do with Maria 's dad 's disappearance .
Why would he kidnap Mr. Osman ? Do you have proof ?
Peace be upon you .
What ?
The police have found Mr. Osman ?
I 'm thankful , Ustaz .
Maria has told me everything .
We already found out
who is causing trouble for our family .
Fazli is right .
Not every religious person
can be trusted .
Just a few rotten apples , not all .
- Don 't be so quick to judge . - I 'm sorry , Ustaz Adam .
There are lots of people out there
who do bad things in the name of religion .
Who are you talking about ?
I don 't know how to tell you this , but you should go and ask my dad .
He is in his bedroom , but his condition has become worse .
It 's better if you go and see my dad . He wants to see you too .
Allow me to go to the room .
Mr. Osman .
What 's all this ?
You said Mr. Osman was in the bedroom .
I couldn 't find him .
Hadn 't the police found him ?
Ustaz Adam .
What are you holding , Ustaz ?
Ustaz , where are you ?
Maria was trying to commit suicide .
I 'm coming back from the hospital .
Ustaz , are you listening to me ?
Ustaz ?
God , have mercy .
My goodness .
Help ! Open the door !
BODY 1
Dear God , lead us away from hypocrisy .
Give my son guidance .
Show him the right path .
Let him know the truth , dear God .
Amen , Lord of the worlds .
Ustaz .
- Wait . - Where 's Maria ?
- Why did she disappear suddenly ? - Where are you going ?
Are you just going to leave ?
What exactly happened ? Do you have any idea who is behind this ?
I 'm sure one of us knows what is going on .
I have no idea at all , Ustaz . Things happened one after another .
You really have no idea at all ?
Are you suspecting me ?
Are you saying that I am the culprit ?
Then , how can you explain this ?
I found this when I was looking through your house .
Please tell me , whose talisman is this ?
Apparently , it was you who took it .
I thought the late Imam Ali was the one who took it .
This talisman is indeed mine .
It protects my family .
I told you before that I sought help elsewhere .
A shaman gave this to me .
We should seek protection only from God
and not from a shaman giving this kind of talisman .
Believing in something other than God is the biggest blasphemy .
Don 't you know that ?
God , have mercy on us .
Maria ?
Hello , Maria ? Where are you ?
I can 't stand this anymore , Ustaz .
You are the only one who can help me .
Please save me , Ustaz .
I have a secret to tell you .
Secret ?
I 'm at the old bungalow in Batu 30 , Ulu Kampung .
- Please come now , Ustaz . - What 's the secret , Maria ?
Maria ?
- Peace be upon you , Dad . - And peace be upon you too . Where are you ?
I want you to come home now . I need to see you .
Shah is here with me .
What is he doing there ?
I 'm sorry , Dad . I have an emergency .
Maria called me just now .
She said she 's at the old bungalow in Batu 30 , Ulu Kampung .
- I 'm going there right now . - Adam , wait .
God , have mercy on us .
Maria !
Ustaz .
- Help me , Ustaz . - Maria , what are you doing here ?
How did you get here ?
We have to get out of here quickly .
Because we seem to have other " visitors " here .
I was trying to find a way out , but I couldn 't .
I couldn 't find my way out , Ustaz .
Please get me out of here .
You couldn 't find a way out ?
It 's okay . Come with me .
Hurry .
I 'm sorry , Ustaz .
- Actually , I - - - Let 's talk outside .
What matters now is that we find a way out .
We were here just now , weren 't we ?
Did we perhaps walk in circles ?
- Oh , God ! - Ustaz !
Oh , God !
Help me !
Goodness , Maria .
Maria !
Maria .
Say your shahada , Maria .
I 'm sorry ...
- There is no deity except God . - I 'm sorry ...
Actually ...
I 'm the one who hit your car .
- I 'm the one who caused your wife 's death . - It was you ?
Why did you do this to me , Maria ?
Why ?
What did I ever do to you ?
Tell me , Maria . I want to know why you did that .
- Tell me . - Since ...
- I ... - Who asked you to do this ?
I 'm the one who forced her to hit your car .
It was you whom I wanted to get rid of ,
but surprisingly , you are hard to be killed .
What did I do , Mr. Osman ?
Because you interfered with my job
to get rid of believers in the village .
I hate people like you .
A bunch of hypocrites !
You are the one who has been harming the village all this time .
Imam Ali was your best friend , you know ?
- God , have mercy ! - I could even kill
my own daughter .
Why not the others ?
She suddenly chose to become a faithful person .
She would not worship what I worship .
That 's why she had to die too .
How could you kill your own daughter ?
She didn 't reveal your doings because she loved you !
You prayed with the villagers at the mosque .
And you gave donations too .
What was all that ? Why ?
You were crippled before this , right ?
I thought people like you are all that .
Turns out , it was easier to fool people like you .
If you want to be rich ,
marry a young and pretty lady ,
and live well like I do ,
- you must worship - - - The cursed Satan !
To kill Muslims and become rich with dirty money ?
It 's better to have no money than no conscience , Mr. Osman !
Killing Muslims is the deal you made with Satan !
This is the biggest hypocrisy !
You 're a hypocrite !
Hell is your place !
I summon thee forth O , Zannabur .
Come to me , your master who awakened you .
Show yourself , Satan !
Destroy this believer for me .
I summon thee forth O , Zannabur .
Come to your master who awakened you .
I seek refuge in God from Satan the outcast .
Dear , Satan .
In the name of God .
There is no deity except Him .
The Ever-Living , the sustainer of existence .
Neither - -
Oh , God !
Plant those seeds of doubt in your heart , Adam .
- Oh , God . - Nobody can help you here .
I know you have doubts about God .
Show Him your doubts .
Listen to the calling of Satan .
Listen .
Indeed , God is always with me .
And He will never fail those who rely solely on Him .
He will guide me !
I summon thee forth O , Zannabur .
Come to your master who awakened you .
Show yourself , Satan !
Destroy this believer for me .
Oh , God !
- Show yourself , Satan ! - Oh , God !
God doesn 't care about you ! What good has He ever done for you ?
Take your wife for example .
Don 't you get it , Adam ? God has never accepted your faith .
God , help me !
He doesn 't care about you !
He gives nothing in return !
There is no might or power except with God !
Taste your suffering !
Sufficient for us is God , and He is the best Disposer of affairs !
Fill your heart with hatred towards me ,
and also Maria who caused the death of your family !
Don 't forgive Maria ! Tap into the darkness in your heart !
If God should aid you , no one can overcome you ,
- but if He should forsake you , - Damn you , believers !
who is there that can aid you after Him ?
Oh , God .
All thanks to You .
Indeed we belong to God , and indeed to Him we will return .
God has finally answered my prayers , Dad .
I know who caused Zulaikha 's death .
It was Maria .
Maria did that .
But I chose to forgive her .
I decided to forgive her .
There 's one more thing you need to know , Adam .
I wanted to tell you , but it was hard for me to say
because the truth might upset you .
But today ,
I need to be honest with you .
There 's a reason why I broke into your house that day .
Actually , I 'm the one who asked your dad to come .
I wanted him to take a look at you himself .
That 's why ...
God knows everything .
As long as you don 't forgive them ,
you won 't be at peace .
If God is willing ,
once you have forgiven the person who did this ,
God will guide you .
God will open your heart ... and your eyes to the truth .
I have tried to tell you .
But you
did not even give me
a single chance to tell you
that Amir ...
is gone .
Oh , God !
Just like Zulaikha .
Adam !
God , have mercy on us .
Dear Almighty God
of All-Living and All-Sustaining .
I ask for Your boundless blessings to help me .
To correct my mistakes .
Never for a second
leave me alone to my trouble .
Lift me off my woes and worries .
As a humble servant ,
I cannot handle them by myself .
God , please forgive me .
I beg for Your forgiveness with all my heart .
Subtitle translation by Kelvin Chan